I'm the rabbi, you're not, so what do you say?
Kapooros is not the Torah.
Show me where Kapooros is in the Torah.
Show me the Torah where it says to swing a chicken over your head
and slit its throat to absolve you from your sins before Yom Kapoor.
Show me the verse.
First go, learn your own Judaism, and then we'll...
I know the Tanakh very well.
You put tfile in tomorrow?
You can put tfile on tomorrow?
I don't understand what you're saying.
Are you Jewish by any means?
I studied the Tanakh.
I'm not Jewish by heritage.
Okay, so you're not Jewish, you don't know Halakha.
True?
You don't know Halakha.
He asked you where in the Torah it says to do this.
You know Torah is bigger than five books of Moses?
Excuse me.
That's the source of it.
It's way bigger than that.
So what is the source of this?
What's the source of this?
Educate me.
Go open up books.
You don't know here, but I'm not going to argue with you.
Tell me which one.
No, I'm just saying do not steal because you agree that steal is wrong
and they just stole and they covered their face while they're doing it.
True?
I'm not doing that.
Okay, they just did that.
It's not stealing.
And he's being murdered.
He's trying to say that they're right.
True?
Thank you for not taking a video.
While you're speaking to me, you're actually not taking a video of it.
Amazing.
Thank you very much.
Hey, lo titsarak.
Lo titsarak.
Like what?
You're pronouncing it totally wrong, so I don't even understand what you're saying.
Okay, then tell me how to pronounce it.
I don't know what you're saying.
Show me how to pronounce it.
Do not murder.
Lo.
Okay, and then it says in a different passage, you have to do it.
It's perfect.
You're saying it wrong, so I don't understand what you're saying.
Okay, so tell me how to say it right.
I don't know what he's saying.
What is he saying?
Do not murder.
You said it wrong.
The sixth commandment.
The sixth of the ten words.
Speaking about animals have ruach and nefesh.
Also, which scripture?
You sound like you're so Jewish, I'm like.
Can you tell me what scripture this is in?
Are you Jewish?
I am.
Are you putting on the phone tomorrow?
No.
But it says in the scriptures that you're meant to put on the phone.
I know.
The scriptures say a lot of stuff.
So why don't you do that?
And oh, suddenly.
I don't follow the scriptures.
Suddenly.
So don't come to us that we do follow the scriptures.
No, I want to know.
And you're coming to us with a complaint that we are following the scriptures.
First, learn your own scriptures that you are Jewish.
So tell me which one I can read.
You're the one that's not burning.
Right, right, right.
True.
Put on the phone tomorrow and then we'll argue it out.
So you won't speak to me unless I put on the tabella.
If you don't agree with your own Torah, why are you coming to me and arguing with it?
Because the Torah has been stepped on, my friend.
Yes, it was a step on.
You're the one stepping on it by not putting on the phone.
No, no, no.
Jeremiah 8, verse 8.
I'm speaking with him right now.
You're not the one that's Jewish.
I'm not going to argue that with you.
I'm telling you that I know the scriptures as well as you do.
Who are we to think we have the law of the Lord, the Torah, and that we are wise when the lying pen of the scribes has falsified it?
No, but you hold different things to me.
He's quoting the Tanakh.
I'm quoting Jeremiah 8, verse 8.
Meanwhile, you didn't quote to me a single passage.
Yes, Jeremiah.
You didn't say it correctly.
Jeremiah.
Who are we to know, who are we to think we are wise and have the law of the Lord, the Torah?
That is right.
That is correct.
Open it up on your phone right now.
When the lying pen of the scribes has falsified it, has made it into a lie, what are the lies in the Torah?
How long can I get you?
What are the lies in the Torah?
Jeremiah answers us.
And Jeremiah 7, verse 22.
But I dare you.
Come to God 770.
You know the big synagogue over there?
Come over there.
Put it on the phone, and then we'll speak it out.
So what would the synagogue think about?
Tomorrow morning is the day before Yom Kippur, right?
Yeah.
It's the holiest day of the year.
The day that every single Jew fasts for all his sins.
So put on tefillin.
It's a big, for every man, it's a big mitzvah.
Well, this is a mitzvah too, according to you guys.
So we'll speak it out.
But I first want you to do that.
This makes no sense to me.
You put on the phone tomorrow morning.
We'll speak it out.
Well, you could...
That's it?
How do you justify this with Jeremiah 7, verse 22?
That in the day I called your fathers out of Egypt,
I did not command them concerning burnt offerings or sacrifices.
But this I commanded him.
Obey my voice.
I have like four cameras right now.
He's not even listening.
And a mic.
Not even listening.
He asked you a great question.
He asked you a really good question.
He has a...
Can you not answer the question?
No, it's fine.
Because I know that every single video that's taken of me
usually gets retorted and you take a little passage,
you edit it nicely.
I'm not going to answer it because you guys don't use the right videos.
You guys take one thing that I said...
Just speak truth then.
Just speak truth.
I won't edit it.
Yeah.
What does Jeremiah mean?
After a few years ago, you guys brought a truck over here.
What does Jeremiah mean by God did not command sacrifices?
And totally messed up every single video that you guys took.
That's it.
What does Jeremiah mean?
What does Jeremiah mean by God did not command sacrifices?
I'm telling him.
If he comes putting on filling, I'll speak it out with him.
But he's...
That's it.
I dared him.
Yeah, but he's in agreement with what I'm saying.
I said I'll speak it out with him tomorrow morning if he comes putting on filling.
Okay, then tell him what Jeremiah is.
And as many people are going to be more than happy to speak it out with him.
If people don't tell him.
Tell him what Jeremiah is.
That's it.
Explain to me, what does the filling do?
What is that?
The filling, it says in the scriptures, it's a black box.
Why is it black?
It's actually given to Moses since Mount Sinai.
We know from generation to generation about the black.
And it has parchment inside.
It's written the holy scriptures of Shema.
You heard of Shema?
Yeah.
So it has Shema inside.
Put on your forehead and arm to connect your mind and body and your heart and mind to God.
I can't do that otherwise?
I can't connect my mind, heart, body and God otherwise?
It's a specific way of doing it.
Through prayer and fasting?
True.
God commanded us to do it this way and it's a better way of connecting ourselves.
Did King David do that?
Every single Jew did it.
King David did that?
Yeah.
He put on every single thing.
Where does it say that?
It says it in the passage.
It says put on the fill in on your arm and...
It's a commandment from the Torah.
I think that the Torah is the ten words.
The Torah is the ten words.
The 613 are traditions of men.
No, those are the words and everything else after that.
I love all the Torah, rabbis and all the...
I love the Shema.
Here in Israel, the Lord our God is one.
One meaning?
One God.
One.
And it cannot be separated from the Ruach in me, the Ruach in you.
Why does it say that?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Because we're in the image of God, no?
The bags are still moving right now.
I've got a lot of that footage.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's disgusting, bro.
These chickens are escaping, man.
Mandi, come around.
Here, here.
Oh my God, bro.
Now's the time when you pick until I can not be okay.
Come on.
Look, when the enemy comes in, you're dropping in the bottom of the window.
I didn't get it.
Are you slaughtering them like inhumane or something?
Yeah.
The way they're being slaughtered is inhumanely?
The fact that they're being slaughtered in...
Do you know how sharp that knife is?
The fact that they're being slaughtered in general is inhumane.
Are you vegan?
I am.
Makes sense.
I'm not out of humane.
A good shepherd cares for the life of his sheep.
What?
That's a good tag.
For what?
Nothing.
Dianne?
King David said that.
I was a son of a man.
Dianne is here.
Are you a reporter?
Sorry?
Yeah.
For what?
The internet.
Which?
For who?
What?
I'll cover right there.
What are you doing with that?